Olesia Pryhun

Junior front-end developer

PORTFOLIO

My detailed portfolio with pet projects: https://pryhun.me.

My last project: fake online shop with a local Next.js API, connected to MongoDB.

ABOUT ME

I finished a front-end course, then I continued my studies with a mentor (experienced web developer). He provided me with support and guidance throughout the whole process.

I learned through building projects, making mistakes and fixing them. I used all tools possible: from docs and forums to YouTube and chatGPT.

SKILLS

Front-end: Back-end

- MongoDB
- React Next.js API
- Redux

Next.js

- Bootstrap
- Sass/Scss
- Java Script
- CSS
- HTML

Other

- Git + Bash
- ESLint
- Postman



- pryhun.o@gmail.com
- Telegram: @Pryhun Olesia
- <u>LinkedIn</u>

LOCATION

- Ukraine, Kyiv
- Or remote work

LANGUAGE

- English C1 (CAE Certificate)
- Ukrainian (native)

EDUCATION

Online front-end course (SheCodes)

2023

Online QA Manual course (Hillel)

2022

Kyiv National Linguistic University

Bachelor of Language and Literature (Japanese) 2015 - 2019

HOBBIES

- Jigsaw puzzles
- Coloring books
- Board games

EXPERIENCE

Building pet projects and studying 2023-2024

English Teacher

2019-2022

Language courses

· I taught teenagers and adults English, individually and in groups, offline and online.